are you guys tired of dealing with dmx
cables
or having to gaff every single cable on
the floor on the pipes
we have the solution for you chavez has
come out with the d5
xlr pack so that you can turn all your
fixtures into wireless dmx
so we're back with another video and the
chavez
d5 xlr pack as i mentioned can convert
your lighting rig into full wireless
communications it extends on the d5
platform that chauvet has built upon for
years and years
starting with the d5 hub here and then
they had the d5
usb and then they built in the the d5
and the freedom series but we'll get to
that in a second
first of all let's talk about the d5 xlr
pack it comes with one transmitter and
three receivers and the charging station
so it charges easily by just placing it
on
and the transmitter actually can fully
charge in about four hours and lasts you
about 11 hours of total max time usage
on the battery the receivers charge
fully charged in about two and a half
hours and
they can run up to 10 hours so just make
sure you don't overcharge your units
because you want to preserve the life of
your battery
next we can go over some of the form
factor it's a it's a very convenient
to plug it right into your controller or
your lights
so as you can see it has the xlr it's
got an on off button right here
and it's got a menu button which allows
you to select
your your 2.4 gigahertz channel has 16
channels 16 different channels
so this one operates a little bit easier
in that it's color coded right here
so you'll see the color code on the
little lights
over here and it'll tell you which
channel you're on
from the manual you could see which
color code
corresponds to which number channel so
in case you have to sync it with the
freedom series
like say channel 16 like all four lights
will be on so that'll be your
designation on on the channels as you
can see here
as we have here green means fully
charged and then red means that it's
charging
so that's that's it about this this is
this is a nice little small unit as you
can see it looks like
uh size of a pack of gum and you can fit
in your pocket
but these are great
the range on these guys is about 50
meters or 165 feet
and whereas the range we should point
out on the d5 hub
is about 600 feet so it's
this still is perfectly great to use
in that it all works all together so
anything you have in terms of lighting
chauvet makes these
items so that you can continue to use
their products as long as you want to
use them
and this is their way of making your
pars or your traditional lights that
don't have
a wireless dmx wireless
and your controller so we'll we'll show
you how to connect it all right now
simple as that and i'm going to take one
here and plug it into the
intimidator spot 260 so that we can have
wireless
connection here so now we're going to
start uh controlling everything with the
obey 40
with the d5 xlr uh we're going to start
with the intimidator 260 right here
temperature spot 260
and we have
control of the light
simple with the d5 xlr receiver
and just the power cable simple next we
have the
slimpar pro h
and then continuing on to the freedom
series we have the freedom h1 right here
we have bam and then we have on the
freedom par here bam
and then we have
the freedom psych so as you can see it
integrates so seamlessly
it was just so easy to use couldn't be
easier
like i said it's super wireless it
charges very
easily it's perfect for it's a perfect
add-on product for any
uh system any mobile dj any of any
production company
and um highly recommend it at 279.99
um you can buy more transmitters and
receivers
at 59.99 if you got anything out of this
video please hit the thumbs up below
and please subscribe and hit the
notification button so that you can see
more of this video and more of this
content check out our instagram page for
fun and uh interesting content
and we'll see you in the next video